Maybe for you
there's a tomorrow.
there's 1,000 or 3,000
or 10.
So much time
you can bathe in it.
you can waste it.
But for some of us,
there's only today.
And what you do
today matters.
In the moment,
and maybe into infinity.
But I didn't know any of that
until right before I fell.
The thing is,
you don't get to know.
You don't wake up with a bad
feeling in your stomach
or see shadows move.
If you're like me, you wake
up 24 minutes and 47 seconds
before your best friend is
supposed to be picking you up.
If you're like me,
your last day
starts like this.
Well,
I'll let you know by noon.
Well, I can't organize
a playdate before...
You want something to eat?
No. I'm good.
Sammy, you like
the bird I made you?
Morning.
Sammy!
What?
You forgot
your gloves!
Izzy, how many times
do I have to tell you?
Don't touch my stuff.
Go back inside.
It's cold.
Hey, sexy. Get in!
Okay.
I love the sky
on mornings like this.
Hey.
Greasy forehead,
window, off.
I'm gonna try
not to be depressed
because I'm single
on Cupid Day.
That's Valentine's Day
to you!
Do you have insomnia
or something, Linds?
Excuse me?
It's just cute that you get up
before us and get breakfast.
Ooh.
Did she just call me cute, Kingston?
I believe she did, Edgecomb.
Mmm-mmm.
Al, Linds doesn't do "cute."
No.
It's not in her lexicon.
Lexicon? Nice word choice.
Whoo!
Come on.
Seriously?
Okay, this was maybe funny the
first bazillion times you did it.
It's still funny.
It still is.
Still funny!
Love it. Every time.
Yeah, baby!
No texting and driving.
Don't worry. I'd never let
my best friend die a virgin.
Ooh!
You didn't think
we'd forget, did you?
It's the big day,
opening night.
Rob texted me.
He said, "I made my bed for you."
That is so sweet.
Yes.
No glove, no love.
You hear me?
Take it!
Take it! Take it!
Take it! Take it! Take it!
Shh! Okay, okay...
- Watch the road. Oh, my God.
- Lindsay!
All right. I'm sorry.
We're fine. We're fine.
You're crazy!
We're freakin' fine.
Go ahead
and say we're through
I don't care,
I'll just get another you
I'll get another dude
that look like you
I don't
need you and you don't need me
Give me back my house key
You can leave it
with my new boyfriend
You can leave it on the back
back, back porch
I don't care, when you
leave it leave a message
A message,
a message, a message
You used to never
get the message
Yeah, I talk shit
Yeah, she's talkin' shit
Go ahead
and say we're through
I don't care
I'll just get another you
I'll get another dude
that look like you
I don't need you
and you don't need me
Give me back my house key
My house key
This could be easy
How many roses did you
get last year, Linds?
Twenty-two.
I'm going for 25
this year, though,
and more than one of them
better be from Patrick.
Did I tell you
I sat next to Rob,
and I had to make him fill
out the request form?
It was depressing.
I'd be happy with 15.
I'm not ashamed to admit it.
Last year, Matt literally
sent me a dozen red roses.
Matt, oh, come on.
You just spent
a whole week crying
in the same pair of
sweatpants and it got dark.
We're not going
back there.
No, I've told you a thousand
times, I'll say it again,
you do not need
that loser. Honestly.
Mmm-mmm. Nope.
You got your real baes here.
Mmm-hmm.
We love you. Come here.
Till death do us part.
Even then.
Oh, get in here.
Mmm.
All right, bitches,
let's move!
Sisyphus, not an STD.
What's he like?
What does it mean when something
is described as being Sisyphean?
Does it mean pointless?
Brave?
Late?
Uh, sorry, it was an
emergency and a tribulation.
It was a minor
LaserJet explosion.
Hope the printer survived.
All right,
back to Sisyphus.
What's his character like?
Does he learn from
pushing that boulder...
Hey.
Val-a-gram delivery.
Happy Cupid Day.
Go ahead.
Relax, it's just roses.
Aw, no roses
for Anna.
Is that from your boy?
It's from Rob. Yeah.
All right, all right. Keep it down.
Keep it down, people.
It's so beautiful.
I'm in heteronormative hell.
Okay, okay,
let's hope third time's the charm. Okay?
Sisyphus.
Back to Sisyphus, class.
Yo, Sam.
Hey.
Man.
Sam, hey.
Hi.
Did you like it?
Like what?
Hey, so, um,
big party tonight.
Mom is going out of town.
Whoa.
A huge rager, you know.
Why don't you come, yeah?
I don't know
what my plans are,
like, what everyone else
ends up doing...
So I'll see you tonight.
I don't think so.
Yeah? You know the address.
No. Kent...
Smooth.
- Did you guys hear about Anna?
- You mean bull dyke.
Please say she tripped
over her nose.
Not yet, but her
girlfriend saw this Snap
that we posted
with her and that girl.
She straight up
dumped her.
See?
What?
This is why I deserve
some public recognition,
for making shit
like that happen.
Maybe someone should
give me a ribbon.
Like the ones that you used
to have hanging on your wall,
Sammy, remember,
from horseback riding?
I was, like,
ten years old, Lindsay.
God, Sam, you were
such a nerd back then.
Okay, but isn't it weird
how that stuff happens?
How things connect
in strange ways?
Like if Lindsay
didn't post that Snap...
She deserved it.
I'm just saying,
it's kinda crazy now.
I saw this video about chaos
in the universe... Listen!
How a bird flapping its
wings in South America
can create a major
rainstorm in New York.
Like how one person can watch a
pretentious video about chaos
while three other people
actually die of boredom.
It wasn't a YouTube tutorial,
so you guys wouldn't get it anyway.
Owie!
Samantha Kingston.
- Hi.
- Hey, Rob.
Did you get my rose?
I did.
Who are
these ones from?
Your competition.
I want to see.
Oh, Sam has no competition, Rob.
You know it.
Okay. Well, neither do I, so I guess
we're perfect for each other.
So you're going to
that thing at Kent's tonight?
I heard he's getting a couple kegs.
I don't know.
Yes!
I'll text you later.
One more.
No, I'm eating!
Get out!
Go.
Bye.
You all are too cute.
It's gross.
Mmm.
Oh, you guys!
Tonight our widdle Sammy
passes into womanhood.
I am so proud.
Shh! Stop it.
I hope you shaved.
Oh, my God.
Don't forget to pee
before and after.
Guys, guys, sociopath,
12 o'clock.
Oh, God. Does she
know what a brush is?
No.
Norma Bates!
Hey, did she get
her Val-a-gram?
In chem, I was sitting
right behind her.
What'd she say?
Does she say anything ever?
Well, what'd she do?
She tossed it
right after class.
She really should
appreciate it more.
It's probably the only rose
she'll ever get.
Maybe it had something
to do with the card.
"Maybe next year,
but probably not."
That's it, guys!
Go, girl.
I love it!
It kinda looks like you
put it on your cheeks.
It's the same color.
Yeah. That's the point.
Mmm.
Love it.
It's so effing good.
Can I post this one?
No.
Don't laugh at me.
Okay.
Linds?
Were you nervous
your first time?
I was too drunk
to be anything.
Don't freak out
if it hurts.
Especially at first.
And don't tense up, because
that only makes it worse.
Great. That sounds
really romantic.
Don't worry. It's not like
Rob is some random guy.
You actually like him.
Right. Yes.
Everyone wants to
hook up with him.
Yeah.
Tonight, everything changes.
That face.
Baes!
What are you doing?
What do you think you're doing?
Fart's house
is actually kinda nice.
If I had known,
I would have stopped
calling him Danny DeVito
all year.
Sam and you.
Hey, I'm gonna go find Patrick.
Will you be okay?
What?
I'm gonna go find Patrick.
Will you be okay?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Mwah!
Hey, Sam!
You made it.
Sam! Sam!
Hi!
Oh, I am sorry.
Let me get that for you.
How drunk are you?
I'm not drunk.
Don't worry about it.
Know what?
You're the hottest girl in here.
The hottest.
Okay, look, I'm only gonna be
here like an hour, an hour tops.
You know?
You text me and we'll go.
We're just gonna go.
Just me and you. Okay.
Oh, my... Okay. Sorry.
Oh.
What happened?
Nothing.
I'll see ya later, okay?
Elody's really
embarrassing herself.
Elody's a slut.
Lindsay's a bitch
and a drama queen.
I'm rich and have ADD.
Baes!
Bae!
Come on.
Oh, get in here, baby!
Patrick, will you go get me something
a little bit stronger than this beer?
What's the magic word?
Blowjob.
BRB.
Thank you.
Where have you been? I've been
looking everywhere for you.
Have you?
Yes!
Like in Patrick's mouth?
Oops.
What? Oh, she's so shitfaced!
No, you're shitfaced,
shitface.
I can't believe high
school's almost over.
Aw.
Well, actually, we did it right,
you know?
Kissed the hottest boys,
went to the sickest parties.
Do you think we'll
remember any of this?
I mean, like two years,
three years from now?
I won't even
remember this tomorrow.
Oh, my God.
What's she doing here?
Up.
Okay.
Hello, sweetie.
Is that your first drink?
You really should
take it easy.
You're a bitch!
Excuse me?
Whoa.
You heard me.
You're a goddamn fetid bitch
just like your mother.
It's no wonder
Daddy left. Huh?
- You're a bitch, too.
- What?
You're a drunk.
And you...
You're just pathetic.
You know what?
We'd rather be bitches
than a psycho.
Yeah, psycho.
Have you noticed
that nobody likes you?
- Yeah, psycho.
- Psycho.
Has anyone at this party...
- Has anyone talked to you?
- I don't think so.
You weren't even invited.
That's 'cause
you're a freak.
Go back to the ward.
Go home.
Get off me! Get off me!
Who are you?
You're the bitch!
Psycho!
Get this bitch
on a leash!
Psycho!
You wanna go?
Freak, get out of here!
Go!
Go back to the ward,
you psycho bitch!
Are you okay?
What the hell
was that about, huh?
I don't know.
She just called us bitches...
What did she do?
...in front of everybody.
So you attack her?
Okay. This is not my fault!
You gang up
and pour beer all over her?
You know what...
Who are you? Come on...
Do not touch me.
You know, your boyfriend's
throwing up in my sink.
So, you wanna
take care of that?
Come on. Come on!
That was insane.
I'm sorry about Rob, bae.
Music!
Pacific Northwest, my ass.
I hate this weather.
Do you guys wanna get some food?
I really need carbs.
You sound like
my grandmother.
Meh.
Here.
Oh, I like this song.
She called us bitches.
I guess we are.
What time is it?
Did you see
that look in her eyes?
- I mean, she just snapped.
- Yeah.
She freaked me out.
Sam, you're 20 minutes late!
Let's shake it, sister!
Sammy, you like the bird
I made you?
Mommy says
you have to get up.
It's Saturday.
Mommy, Sammy won't get up!
Don't make me
come up there.
Yeah?
Sexy lady!
What are you doing?
I'm so sorry. I had a nightmare,
so it's a slow start.
Um...
What happened last night?
Oh. Sorry. I was FaceTiming
with Patrick till, like, 3:00.
Speaking of which,
are you nervous for tonight?
What?
You, Rob,
his flannel sheets?
I'm gonna shower.
Nope, no time. Come on.
It's Cupid Day.
Whoo!
Seriously?
Okay, this was maybe funny the
first bazillion times you did it.
It's still funny.
Yeah, baby!
Nice tits!
Ooh. I have your present.
No glove, no love.
You hear me?
It goes on him.
Sisyphus, not an STD.
All right. Keep it down.
Keep it down, people.
It's so beautiful.
I'm in
heteronormative hell.
Thank you, girls. Thank you.
Okay, okay, let's hope
third time's the charm.
Yo, Sam.
Oh, man.
Sam, you forgot this one.
No, I didn't forget it.
What do you mean?
The more roses
you get on Cupid Day,
the more popular
you are, right?
Thanks for the tip, Kent.
Noted.
Well, I didn't say
the rose was from me.
But it is
from you, right?
Well...
Anyway, my mom is
out of town...
Out of town and
you're having a party?
Yeah. Do you
wanna come? Or...
I have to go.
Well, see you tonight? Or...
Are you nervous?
No, no, no, no, no.
You don't want to waste the first
night you go full womanhood.
Okay,
you sure they look good?
I just really don't want to look
like I'm trying too hard, you know?
You're fine.
Such a weird day.
Like how?
Just weird.
I feel like I'm still dreaming
from yesterday, like...
Or maybe yesterday was the dream.
I don't know... Whoa.
You're awake now!
No, no, no, no!
Sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Don't. Don't do that.
Oh, my God, there's so many
hot guys here tonight!
I'm gonna go
find Patrick, okay?
What?
I'll be right back!
Sam! Hey, you made it!
Sam. Sam.
Oh, I am sorry.
Let me get that for you.
Rob, I need to talk to you.
What?
About what? What's up?
I'm feeling pranked.
Tonight was supposed to be
our special night...
No, no, no, no, no. Rob?
What?
I don't feel good.
I'm freaking out.
It's always something.
Can we go talk some...
...where?
Okay, Sam. Okay. I'm gonna
fill my cup up first.
Five minutes.
Can you wait that long?
This room is off limits.
I was just looking
for the bathroom.
Sorry.
I feel like I'm having déjà
vu with you being in my room.
Oh, my God, I've been having
déjà vu all day long.
Are you okay?
Yeah. Excuse me.
I've been looking
everywhere for you.
Yeah?
In Patrick's mouth, maybe.
You seem a little guilty.
Were you with Rob, you hussy?
Skank.
Harlot.
Hey, are you guys
talking about me?
You know what?
I think I'm gonna go home.
No, no, no!
What?
You don't have to drive me.
It's okay. I'll find a ride.
No, we just got here.
I'm confused.
I thought you were supposed
to get it on with Rob tonight.
Yeah.
Yeah, I changed my mind.
Well, at least I'm not
gonna be the only virgin.
Oh, my God.
What's she doing here?
Watch this.
Is that your first drink?
You're a bitch!
Just like your mother.
No wonder Daddy left. Huh?
- You're a bitch, too.
- What?
You're a drunk.
And you...
You're just pathetic.
Juliet...
You know what? We'd rather
be bitches than a psycho.
Yeah, psycho.
Have you noticed
that nobody likes you?
- Yeah, psycho.
- Psycho.
Has anyone at this party...
- Has anyone talked to you?
- I don't think so.
- Go back to the ward.
- Go home.
Go home.
Get off me!
Go to hell!
Freak, get out of here!
Get the fuck out!
Get this bitch
on a leash!
Psycho! Psycho.
You wanna go?
Go back to the ward,
you psycho bitch!
What do you think
people will say about you
when you die?
Like I care.
I'm serious.
That we're hot.
This shit is morbid, Sam.
Hey, watch the road.
Hey.
We need music.
You watch the road.
Guys, I'll find a song.
I want to help you
pick a song.
Okay, mom.
Guys, wait.
Don't elbow me.
Just pick something.
You're trouble.
You always have to pee.
'Cause she drinks
too much.
That, and she has the
bladder of a baby squirrel.
The truck.
Truck?
Watch out for the truck.
What truck?
How did you...
It wasn't a dream.
It really happened. Again.
Sammy, you like the bird
I made you?
It's origami.
Mommy says
you have to get up.
Tell Mom I'm sick.
You don't feel hot.
Stop it.
Let go!
Mommy,
Sammy won't get up!
It wasn't until then
that I allowed myself
to think the worst.
Sam?
What's this about you
feeling sick?
I just don't feel good.
On Cupid Day?
Did something happen?
I don't know.
Did you and Rob
have a fight?
No. Mom, go away.
Please don't use that tone.
I'm just trying to help.
I just need to sleep
a little bit longer.
Please?
Okay. Well, I'll let Lindsay
know that you're going in late.
But I have to be
at work by 10:00.
Thank you for driving me.
Sure.
Sammy...
Hmm.
You'll feel better once you
see some of your roses.
I don't know. Maybe.
Well, you're lucky
to be so popular.
When I was a senior,
I hadn't even kissed a boy.
Everyone said my eyes
were too close together
and that I looked
like a fish.
Yeah.
I have to
get to work, honey.
I think you're beautiful.
Go.
Bye.
Maybe
everything was connected.
Maybe a flock of birds
could cause a rainstorm
and everything done
could be undone.
Maybe things could change.
And maybe
I could change them.
It's Rob.
We're having issues.
But it's the day.
The note in his
Val-a-gram said "Love ya."
"L-U-V ya. Luv ya."
What is that? We've been
going out since last year.
Yeah. Well, you know, maybe he's just
waiting to say it, like, tonight.
I'm not gonna
have sex with him
just so that he says
"I love you."
I'm not gonna
do that.
We go out every weekend.
Mmm.
I don't know.
I wanna stay in.
Like we used to.
Okay, but the only reason
we stayed in
was because we weren't invited
to any senior parties.
I just, bottom line, don't want to
have to deal with that today. Okay?
Okay.
All right.
What are you doing?
- What is she...
- Don't worry.
Are you texting...
Oh, my God.
That devilish grin,
though.
Oh, my God.
What? What?
Why did he give me that...
What did you say?
Relax, I just told him
that you got your period.
That's a good one. Yes.
That's perfect.
- You're welcome!
- That's a good one.
Lock up the knives
and babies!
Does it smell
like pee in here?
Yeah, I can smell her
from here.
Remind me again.
Why do we hate Juliet?
Are you serious?
We don't hate her. It's just she's super
creepy with all those weird drawings.
Remember Mellow Yellow
in the fifth grade?
Oh, my God.
When Lindsay found out that
she peed in her sleeping bag
on the Girl Scout trip.
Why do you care
all of a sudden?
You know she should be
institutionalized.
I was just wondering.
That's all.
So, we're going over
to your house, right?
Obviously.
Can I borrow
something?
Always. I got you.
Hey. Uh, these came for you
in Daimler's class.
I know I'm not wearing
the appropriate attire,
but I promise
they're legitimate.
Cool.
Also, uh, this rose
came for you.
It's kind of like
a painting of a rose.
You know, it stands out
in front of all the others.
Thank you.
Hey, I never said
that it was from me.
But, whoever it was from,
they put a lot of thought into it. So...
By the way, my mom is
out of town this weekend,
so I'm gonna throw
a big party tonight.
Yeah.
Did you remember the address?
Or do you...
Hey, Sam.
It was third grade, so you
probably don't remember.
But do you, uh...
You think you'll come? Or...
No, I can't. Sorry.
Oh, come on.
Well, I'm... I could have
crutches on call for you,
in case you want to climb
up the tree... Kent.
...and play flying squirrel.
That was one time.
Look, I'm just saying. I'm prepared.
I'm prepared.
Okay, glad to hear it.
So, that's a maybe, or...
I don't think so.
Well, I'll take
that "No" as a "Maybe."
So, maybe
I'll see you tonight.
Oh, God.
Juliet Sykes
just arrived at the party.
Gross.
Yeah. The worst.
I'm so glad we didn't go.
Mmm. Snapchat alert. Rob is totally
puking in the kitchen sink.
Oh, I want to see that.
I wanna see that.
Of course he is.
- I don't wanna see it. It's gross.
- Ew.
You kiss that?
I can't believe you made
this ice cream, Ally.
It's literally better
than a restaurant's.
No, it's true.
I mean, you should
go to cooking school.
Screw college.
Thanks, guys.
It has no dairy.
Oh, you're so full
of shit.
Thirty-eight.
- Okay.
- You can shut up now.
What?
Matt's at the party.
Ally, you say "Matt"
one more time
and I will kill you
in your sleep.
I will kill you
12:39.
I wonder what filter
Terri uses on her photos.
Major FOMO.
Such a loser.
Ugh, Steve's flirting
with a freshman.
I love you guys.
Aw, Sam...
We love you, too.
Aw, we love you, Sam.
Weirdo.
Don't go emo on us.
Shit. Where's my phone?
Juliet Sykes is dead.
She killed herself.
But nothing happened
to her at the party.
How totally insane.
Could our rose have
something to do with it?
Don't be stupid.
God, imagine how
her family feels.
Look, you can't be mean
to someone forever
and then just feel badly
when they die, okay?
We all knew she was crazy.
God, Lindsay, she was your
best friend in fifth grade.
Yeah, I remember you used
to sleep over at her house.
Yeah, well, that was before
she became a sociopath, Ally.
I'm going back to sleep.
I'm going to sleep
in my room.
I'm going with her.
You were friends
with Juliet?
No one even talked
to you in fifth grade,
and I don't hold that
against you.
You never said anything.
We made fun of her
for all these years...
It's not our fault.
Go to sleep.
I did everything right.
And nothing changed.
I woke up this mornin'
Didn't recognize
the boy in the mirror
Then I laughed and I said
Oh silly me, that's just me
Then I proceeded to brush
some stranger's teeth
But they were my teeth
and I was weightless
Just quivering like some leaf
come in the window of a restroom
I couldn't tell you what the
hell it was supposed to mean
'Cause it was a Monday,
no, a Tuesday
No, a Wednesday,
Thursday, Friday
Then I woke up this mornin'
The day starts
and ends the same,
regardless of anything
I do or say.
If that's how it works,
I'm gonna do and say
whatever I want.
Oh, no, you're not wearing
that to school.
My Cupid Day outfit.
Yeah, well, you don't want to
give people the wrong idea.
What idea is that exactly?
No, this is not happening.
Go back up and change, please.
This is my life. I'll do whatever
the hell I want with it.
Dan, can you just jump in here, please?
Look, Sam...
That's so disrespectful to
talk to your mom... Hey, Sam!
Here... I told you not
to touch my stuff!
That's it!
You are grounded!
Grounded?
I'm already grounded.
Samantha!
Maybe I was dead
and in hell.
Maybe I was alive
But it didn't matter.
Nothing mattered anymore.
What are you wearing?
Funny.
Excuse me.
Jeez, wake up on the wrong
side of the bed or something?
For a few days now, yep.
Nice tits!
What happened to Sam?
Uh, someone forgot to take her
happy pills this morning.
I took mine.
Well, I know something
that'll cheer you right up.
I swear to God, Elody, if you
hand me a condom right now...
But it's your present.
For your special night.
Take it.
Unless you want to be
a walking STD farm.
You would know.
At least I'm not
still a virgin.
What the hell
is wrong with you?
What did you just
say to me?
What is it? Do you feel like
you need to prove to us
that you don't give a shit?
Is that what it is?
'Cause guess what?
You don't need to prove anything.
We all know that you don't give a
damn about anybody but yourself.
We're all pretty
fucking clear on that!
What the hell is
your problem today, Sam?
You guys, don't fight.
Just drop it.
What, you don't agree?
Leave her out of it.
Why? You're the one who talks shit
about both of them all the time.
"Look at Elody
climbing all over Steve.
"He doesn't even like her.
Look at Ally.
"Oh, my God!
She's such a know-it-all.
"She just loves
the sound of her own voice.
"Hope Elody doesn't
puke in my car again
"and make it smell
like alcoholic."
Stop it, Sam.
Out.
Get out!
Now!
I'd love to hear what you say
about me behind my back.
Sisyphus, not an STD.
Don't say it.
I'm in heteronormative hell.
Okay, thank you.
Thank you, girls. Thank you.
Okay, okay, let's hope third
time's the charm. Okay?
Sisyphus.
Sam! What?
You can take 'em.
Oh, Sam, you're breaking
hearts left and right.
Am I breaking yours,
Mr. Daimler?
What?
Your heart,
am I breaking it?
No. You're not.
My patience, however,
is at its breaking point.
Take a seat. Please.
If you insist.
Okay. Sisyphus.
Sisyphus.
Why is our friend Sisyphus
still relevant today?
Why is the story
Don't even think about it.
Turn around.
That way.
Bye.
Get this bitch
out of here!
Psycho!
What the hell?
Shit.
What are you doing
in here?
This is my bathroom.
Nice shoes.
Hard to walk in, huh?
I can walk in them
just fine, thank you.
Aw, you need
a pair of these.
Comfiest shoes I ever owned.
Really?
All right, your loss.
Whatever.
You wanna trade?
Like, switch shoes?
Come on, Kingston. See if I
can get in those without...
Just get out.
...hurting myself.
Come on, let's try it.
Why not?
What?
Yeah, let's do it.
Come on!
Why do you guys
hate me so much?
I know you know what's written
in this bathroom somewhere.
It's AC...
Equals...
BD, right?
Anna Cartulo
equals bull dyke.
Or maybe it's
"biggest douchebag."
But I reckon that honor definitely
belongs to Lindsay Edgecomb.
So, is that it?
'Cause I'm gay?
I don't know.
Isn't that how
it always works out?
There's somebody laughing, there's
somebody being laughed at.
Right.
Look, whatever.
Really. I mean, this whole high
school thing's just a blip.
I'm not gonna remember
any of you.
I win.
Do you ever feel like you're living
the same day over and over again
with only, like, a few
things being different?
Oh, shit, Samantha.
You just described my whole life!
Hey, what's up?
Hey, Sam.
Did you have to ask
permission to talk to me?
Lindsay's just really upset
about what you said.
You should apologize.
Well, everything that
I said was true, so...
It doesn't matter
if it's true.
She's Lindsay. She's ours.
We're each other's, you know?
Just apologize.
You're not listening to me.
I'm not sorry.
Please, Sam?
Why do you care
so much, Elody?
Because...
You guys are all I have.
Are you still trying
to turn her against me?
You're the horrible driver.
You're the one always criticizing
people and hurting people.
You're the one who lied about
being friends with her
and then tortured her
for all these years.
I just followed along
and yet...
I'm the one paying for it.
Sam, what are you
talking about?
Whoa. What?
Oh, my God.
Sam, I haven't seen you in, like, forever.
Where have you...
Get this bitch
on a leash!
I love you. Is that what
you wanted to hear?
Go back to the ward,
you psycho bitch!
Sam?
Hey, are you okay?
Obviously, you're crying.
But is there something I can do?
I'll get you a tissue.
Yeah, yeah.
Thanks.
Yeah.
Sorry I'm in your room.
I know there's a sign.
No. Don't worry about it.
The sign's just really
for other people,
so they don't get
in my stuff.
It's the first big party
I've ever had, so...
Why'd you have one now?
I figured if I had a party,
you'd come.
I like your room.
Yeah? It's my dad's
old den.
It must get a lot of light.
Yeah.
It's like waking up
in the middle of the sun.
I get to see the old tree.
I like it.
It's constant.
Is that the one
we used to sit in?
Yeah. Yeah, we did.
Do you remember
climbing up it?
And then you jumped down
and sprained your ankle?
I was stupid.
It was very ambitious.
I should go.
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey. Just stay for
a second. Okay?
I can drive you home or...
I don't want to go home.
Okay, well, you can, uh...
You could crash here
if you want.
Not, like, with me.
Somewhere else.
I'll be somewhere else.
Bed completely to yourself.
The Kent McFuller
master suite.
Yeah?
Okay.
Hey, it's okay.
Here.
I'm sorry about earlier.
Don't worry about that.
No, I'm sorry
I've always been
so mean to you.
Don't look.
Don't read it. Please?
Why? It's...
It's something bad.
Okay.
Your skin's so hot.
It's always like that.
I wish we could
be here forever.
Okay, let's try again.
We're taking a day off.
I think you're just
gonna drool around.
What is it?
And then you're just gonna go
through there and then like that.
If I was going to relive
the same day over and over,
I wanted it to
be a worthy day.
But not just for me.
Do the kids at school
ever make fun of you
for the way that you talk?
Sometimes.
You can do
something about that.
You know, you can learn
to talk differently.
But this is my voice. How will
kids even know it's me talking?
When I was
in the fifth grade,
this girl used to
sing this song.
She smells like manure
and she lived in the sewer
Samantha Kingston
Who did that?
Lindsay.
How come
you're so mean to Mom?
I'm not mean to Mom.
You drew a line on
the floor with nail polish
and said
she couldn't cross it.
Mom and I had a fight,
and I was mad at her
in the moment,
but I didn't...
I didn't think that
she'd actually stay away.
Look at that.
That's just the outside,
how pretty it was.
Oh, my gosh.
Look at you guys.
- Can you send those to me?
- Aw!
So cute!
Those are beautiful.
Remember when you used to
come here all the time?
I do. Of course.
Then your daughter
got too cool, so...
- I'm just kidding.
- Can we go watch the pizza?
Okay. Wait, tiger.
I'm glad we did this.
Yeah. It was really sweet
what you did today.
Do you think
I'm a good person?
Of course I think you're a good person.
But it doesn't
really matter what I think.
I mean, what's important
is what you think.
No, I'm serious.
I want to know...
Why do you think
that I'm a good person?
Do you remember when
you were a little girl?
You used to take turns riding
all of the horses in the stable
so that none of them
would feel left out?
Do you remember that?
I do.
Mmm-hmm.
But I was a little girl.
It's different.
But you have a big heart, Sam.
That doesn't go away.
One good thing.
You just focus
on that one good thing,
and you see
where it leads you.
How is it possible
to change so much
and not be able to
change anything at all?
I knew
I had to do something.
Something good.
You made it.
Oh. Sorry.
The room's off limits.
No. Forget the sign.
It's no big deal.
That's really just there
for other people,
so they don't mess
with my stuff.
I'm glad you came.
Yeah. I had to. I like what
you've done with the place.
Yeah, this used to be
my dad's old den.
Now it's the Kent McFuller
master suite.
Yeah, not so good
in the morning, though.
It's like waking up in...
In the middle of the sun.
Yeah.
I hope you don't think
that it's weird
that I'm here
with you right now.
Sam, um...
I once wore Crocs
for 365 days straight,
so I don't think
anything's weird.
I forgot about
your Crocs phase.
Yeah.
Why are you always
so nice to me?
Well, do you remember in third
grade right after my dad died?
We were in the cafeteria
and I was crying,
and Phil Howe came up to me,
called me a baby,
and then smacked my tray
right out of my hand,
and food went
flying everywhere.
I remember what
we were eating, too.
It was, um, mashed potatoes
and turkey burgers.
And you came over,
you scooped up the mashed
potatoes right off the ground
and you went up to
Phil and you smashed
the mashed potatoes
right in his face.
And you then said,
"You're worse than a hot lunch,"
which, at the time,
was a really good insult.
I mean, I didn't laugh
more that day than...
I mean...
It was the first time I laughed
since my dad died and I...
Do you remember
what I said to you?
"You're my hero."
Yeah.
And that day I vowed
to be your hero, too.
No matter how long
it took.
Look, I'm sorry.
No, don't do...
Don't be sorry. It's okay.
Good.
'Cause I'm not really sorry.
Shit.
Wait.
Sam! Hey!
Sam, wait, I...
Oh, my God,
Sam, did you see that?
Hey, Sam.
Did you see
where Juliet went?
Juliet, stop!
Juliet!
Juliet! Wait!
Juliet, wait!
Juliet!
What are you doing?
I know what happened back there.
Get away from me.
And I feel
really bad about it,
and I know
this may sound crazy,
but I have a feeling I may
be able to understand you
better than you think
that I could.
You hate me.
I don't hate you.
I know we haven't always
been the nicest to you,
but the thing is that Lindsay
didn't mean anything by it.
We didn't know
what we were doing.
I used to be friends
with Lindsay.
It was right before
her parents got divorced.
I used to sleep over
at her house.
Her parents would be
fighting so bad.
She was so upset.
She was so upset,
she started wetting the bed.
You remember the name you
all gave me in fifth grade?
The name Lindsay gave me?
"Mellow Yellow."
Remember that?
You remember
the camping trip
when I supposedly peed
in my sleeping bag?
It was Lindsay.
Lindsay's the one
who peed.
When everyone asked
what happened,
she just pointed
her finger at me
and screamed,
"She did it."
Juliet...
Please let me help you.
It doesn't matter now.
Hey.
It's like your Val-a-gram
always said...
"Maybe next year, but...
"Probably not."
Juliet.
For the first time,
when I wake up,
I'm not scared
or confused or angry.
Because, for the first time,
I truly understand what needs to happen.
I truly understand
how to live this day.
Oh, thank you.
Yeah.
Want something to eat?
I'm good, thanks.
Lindsay's got it covered.
Mom?
Oh.
I love you.
I love you, too.
What, no love
for your old man?
I love you, too,
old man.
Thank you.
Sammy, you forgot
your gloves!
What would I do
without you?
Hey.
You are perfect
the way that you are, Fizzy.
Always remember that.
I can't breathe!
It's cold!
Yeah.
What are you doing?
Auditioning for a Tampax commercial?
Let's go.
Yeah, baby!
Nice tits! Get in!
Yes.
You know how I like it.
Hey, Elody.
What, do I have
white stuff on my face?
You know why I love you?
I love you because you're
down for anything. Always.
You know
I'm a down-ass bitch.
You are.
Hey, I'm down, too.
Ooh. Okay.
No, I love you, Ally, because
you're curious about the world.
And you're passionate,
and you are driven.
Did someone swallow Oprah
this morning?
I love you, Linds.
I love you because
you're the kind of friend
that toilet-papers
Jason Foster's house
for a week straight
all by herself
just because he said
that I was a bad kisser.
Asshole.
Oh, uh, I think I know why
Sam's in such a good mood.
Oh.
It goes on him.
Thank you so much
for that.
Sisyphus, not an STD.
Sorry, it was an emergency
and a tribulation.
A minor LaserJet explosion.
Val-a-gram delivery.
Happy Cupid Day.
It's so beautiful.
I'm in heteronormative hell.
I like your boots.
Sisyphus fails every time,
but he still thinks that he'll be
able to push that boulder uphill.
He's imprisoned
by his own hubris.
The only way to escape
is to change.
Be careful.
Oh, man.
Sam. Hey.
Hey.
Um... "You're my hero."
You got a secret admirer?
Secret?
That's not so secret.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Well, um...
Well, hey, listen, I'm having
a party tonight. Mmm-hmm.
And I was wondering if you
maybe wanted to come,
maybe? Yeah? No?
What's in it for me?
Yeah. And, um,
I have something I want to
tell you later. A secret.
Later? Okay.
Yes. Okay.
Wait, the "you're my hero"
thing, how did you...
Thank you for my beautiful rose.
I love it.
What'd you say to me?
This is not working out.
Okay, Sam, you can't
break up with me.
I think I can
and I think I just did.
I should've picked Elody.
What just happened?
You guys were
supposed to...
I mean, you said
you wanted to...
It's Rob Cokran.
He doesn't deserve me.
Nonetheless,
very shocking.
Sociopath,
12 o'clock.
Uh-oh.
Does it smell
like pee in here?
Stop.
Norma Bates!
What?
Just don't.
But it's Juliet.
Exactly, it's Juliet.
She has a name
and she is a person.
Yesterday, you said
you were afraid
she would bite you
if she got too close.
That was
a long time ago.
That was yesterday.
Hey, Linds.
All right,
well, let's do this!
Linds.
What?
How come you never told me
about your parents' divorce?
Are you serious?
Yeah.
Why would I talk about something
that happened a thousand years ago?
Because it happened to you.
And you matter to me.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Come here.
Okay? Let's go inside.
You know you don't have to
act so tough all the time.
Mmm.
Don't worry about me, okay?
I love you no matter what.
Let's get inside.
Okay.
Move, move, move.
Hey, um, you made it.
Come with me.
What? Okay.
What?
I believe
you owe me a secret, right?
I believe I do.
Okay, so let's hear it.
The secret is
yours was the best kiss
that I've ever had
in my entire life.
Um...
But we haven't kissed.
I mean,
not since the third grade.
Better get started then.
I don't have much time.
What was that for?
Because I wanted to.
I love you.
Juliet, I need to
talk to you.
Just for a second.
It's okay. Please?
Actually, I kind of have
somewhere I have to be.
I know what you have
planned for tonight
and I want you to know that you
don't have to do this. Okay?
You don't know anything.
I know that you have
something to tell me.
You have something
to tell all of us.
You're a bitch.
I have been a bitch.
We all have been bitches, and I...
I'm sorry.
I have to go.
Listen to me.
I'm trying to tell you how sorry...
I am sorry.
You said that.
I'm sorry,
but I have to come with you.
Leave me alone!
I can't.
Sam! Sam!
Why did you run away from me?
I can't talk to you right now.
You've been ignoring me for
years, and then you...
You kiss me and then go back
to acting like I'm invisible?
I meant everything
that happened back there.
That's all I can say,
that I meant it,
and I wish it hadn't
taken me so long.
Sam, are you in trouble?
You can trust me.
You can trust me back.
Juliet!
Juliet, don't!
Wait! Wait!
Why? What's going on?
Why are you following me?
Why can't you
leave me alone?
You don't want to die.
You want the pain
to stop.
Stop. You stop.
You don't know me.
You could never understand.
You have a choice, Juliet.
Not everybody gets that.
Sam!
Please let me help you.
Don't you get it?
You can't help me.
I can't be fixed.
You're not the one
who needs fixing.
There is nothing
wrong with you.
Don't let anyone tell you
that there is.
This is just a blip.
Your life will change, Juliet.
If you just hold on
for one more minute.
It's too late.
No, it's not.
It's never too late.
Juliet, stop!
Maybe for you
there's a tomorrow.
there's 1,000 or 3,000
or 10.
But for some of us,
there's only today.
And what you do today matters.
In the moment
and maybe into infinity.
I see only my greatest hits.
I see the things
I want to remember.
And be remembered for.
That's when I realized that
certain moments go on forever.
Even after they're over,
they still go on.
They are the meaning.
Sam?
You saved me.
No.